<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="recuperarcontraseña">Recover Password</string>
    <string name="recuperar">Recover Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="new_user">New User?</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="decline">Reject</string>
    <string name="ciudadverde">Viridian City</string>
    <string name="ciudadazulona">Celadon City</string>
    <string name="ciudadceleste">Cerulean City</string>
    <string name="ciudadacarmin">Verimllon City</string>
    <string name="ciudadafucsia">Fuchsia City</string>
    <string name="ciudadcanela">Cinnabar Island</string>
    <string name="ciudadplateada">Pewter City</string>
    <string name="ciudadazafran">Saffron City</string>
    <string name="Entrenador">Trainer</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="remember_me">Remember me</string>
    <string name="username">User</string>
    <string name="atrás">Go back to menu</string>
    <string name="warning">This app is being developed by 2 students, it will be getting updates periodically, so expect some features not working just yet</string>
    <string name="liderverde">"Giovanni, Gym leader of Viridian City and also leader of Team Rocket uses rock Pokemon, he is a very ambicious person who was to control the world by using Pokemon's "</string>
    <string name="liderazulona">Erika, leader of the Celadon City gym, she is a specialist in plant-type pokémon, her gym is a greenhouse full of flowers</string>
    <string name="lidercarmin">Lt. surge or Lieutenant Surge is the gym leader from Vermillon city. Surge had this The american ray as a nickname, this was while he was on the military wher he would use his electric type pokemons in order to start his plane. Is because of this that his gym is full of electric toers adn all his pokemon are electric type.</string>
    <string name="liderfucsia">Koga, leader of the Fuchsia gym. Apart from being a trainer he has medicine knowledge, he makes his own pills and medication with his poison-type pokemon.</string>
    <string name="liderceleste">Misty, leader of the Cerulean gym, specialised  on water-type pokemon</string>
    <string name="lidercanela">Blaine, the leader of the gym in Cinnabar Island, considered one of the most intelligent persons of the region that uses fire-type pokemon.</string>
    <string name="liderplateada">Brock, leader of the Pewter gym specialised on rock-type pokemon, even though he is gym leader his dream is to become one of the bests pokemon doctors.</string>
    <string name="liderazafran">Sabrina, gym leader from Saffron city, she has psychic pokemon type, she is actress in Teselia apart from being one of the bests singers from the region.</string>
    <string name="textociudadverde">The Viridian City has a huge forrest surrounding the gym, with one of the biggests schools and labs from the region, so as the base of the Team Rocket lead by the gym leader Giovanni</string>
    <string name="textociudadazulona">The Celadon city has lots of shopping centers so as leisure  centers like a Casino or one of the bests restaurants.</string>
    <string name="textociudadceleste">The Cerulean city has a mysterious place in which you can find extraordinary pokemons. You can also find the most important Bicycles shop of the region.</string>
    <string name="textociudadcarmin">The Vermillon city has the biggest port from the region, in there you can find the most luxurious boats so as famous ones</string>
    <string name="textociudadfucsia">The Fuchsia city has the widest variety of pokemons thanks to the Safari Zone.</string>
    <string name="textociudadcanela">"The Cinnabar Island is the most important, in ther you can find a volcano which is right now not active, so as the most importat labs. Tho the island it is the most important right now it is  completely uninhabited "</string>
    <string name="textociudadplateada">The Pewter city has the largest science museum from the region. This museum has a wide range of pokemon-fossils.</string>
    <string name="textociudadazafran">The Saffron city is the biggest and most populated cities in Kanto, considered the capital of the region as well as being known as The golden thread as it makes reference to its name, it is the city with the most quantity of market</string>
    <string name="gracias">Thanks for playing!</string>
    <string name="Medallas">Medals</string>
    <string name="Entrenadores">Trainers</string>
    <string name="volverlogin">Go back to login</string>
    <string name="arena1">In order to reach this arena you will need between 5 and 10 cards</string>
    <string name="arena2">In order to reach this arena you will need between 10 and 15 cards</string>
    <string name="arena3">In order to reach this arena you will need between 15 and 20 cards</string>
    <string name="arena4">In order to reach this arena you will need between 20 and 25 cards</string>
    <string name="arena5">In order to reach this arena you will need between 25 and 30 cards</string>
    <string name="arena6">In order to reach this arena you will need 30 cards</string>
    <string name="creamazo">Create your deck!</string>
    <string name="nombremazo">Deck name 1</string>

</resources>